# **RESUME**

#### **Personal Detail**

Name: Sachin Baban Shelke

Address: Waman Jadhav Chawl, Shivaji Gally Road No. 12, Hajuri, Thane (W) – 400604

**Email:** shelkesachin2907@gmail.com

**Contact:** 7710817224

Date Of Birth: 29<sup>th</sup> July 1992

Language: Marathi, Hindi, English

**Hobbies:** Reading, Listening Music, Traveling

## **Career Objective**

A result oriented IT Professional with around 2.3 + Years of experience in development and implementation of web application using PHP, CSS, AJAX, JAVASCRIPT and MYSQL technology. Having work experience in the following technologies

- Experience in development phase of web applications using Apache (XAMPP / WAMPP).
- 2 Expertise in implementing web technologies using Framework **Laravel** to develop Enterprise software applications.
- 3 Good knowledge in MySQL, Radis
- 4 Others GIT, JIRA, Slack, Asana, Bitbucket, Gitlab, Postman, AWS-ec2, AWS-S3 etc.

## **Education Qualification**

Degree	Year	Institute	University	Grade/Percentage
BE	2016	VIVA Institute Of Technology	Mumbai University	6.00 Pointers
HSC	2010	B. N. Bandodkar College Of Sicence	Maharastra State Board	53.52 %
SCC	2008	S. B. M. Padwal Vidyalaya	Maharastra State Board	80 %

#### **Work Experience**

#### 1. VASTU Housing Finance PVT LTD

**Role:** PHP Developer

Front-end Technology: HTML, Bootstrap, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery

Back-end Technology: PHP, MySQL, Radis, AWS

Third Party libraries: Maatwebsite Excel, String formatter, MPDF

Framework: Laravel (5.2)

**Duration:** 29<sup>th</sup> OCT 2018 – Present

#### 2. Remindnmore Info Com PVT LTD

**Role:** Software Developer

Front-end Technology: HTML, Bootstrap, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery

**Back-end Technology:** PHP, MySQL, Standalone libraries of Laravel (5.6)

**Duration:** 24<sup>th</sup> JAN 2017 - 28<sup>th</sup> OCT 2018

## 3. CROMA (TATA Enterprises)

**Role:** Technical Support

**Duration:** 13<sup>th</sup> SEPT 2013 – 21<sup>st</sup> JAN 2017

# **Academics Projects**

## 1. Campus Placement System:

**Technology:** JAVA, JSP, Servlets, HTML, Bootstrap,

MySQL, CSS, Glassfish Server, Excel Generator Libraries

**Description :** This was the final year project. The basic idea was to select the

right candidate as per there skill & knowledge base. The all selection was depends on the conducted aptitude by colleges as per the result of the aptitude the company can sort the

right candidate for the there job profile and more students can

place from colleges

#### 2. Online Question Paper Generator:

**Technology:** PHP, MySQL, HTML, CSS, Excel Libraries, PDF Generator

**Description:** This was my academics project, The basic idea was to by use of PDF

generate question papers

#### 3. Online Admission Form:

**Technology:** HTML, JavaScript, CSS, Bootstrap, JSP, Servlets

**Description:** This was the basic project on the JSP, Servlets. Basic Idea was to

create the form for registration for admission

# **Official Project**

## 1. Pulse (Vastu Housing Finance):

Technology: PHP, CSS, Laravel (5.2), MySQL, Oracle, AWS, Redis, PHP OPPS, Payment

Gateways. Javascript, Jquery, WAMP, LAMP

Description: This is the commercial project from VASTU

# 2. SocietyNmore:

Technology: PHP, CSS, Standalone Laravel (5.6), MySQL, AWS, PHP OPPS, Javascript,

Jquery

# **Extra-Curricular Activity**

- 1. Participated in sports of VIT in 2013.
- 2. Participated in the sports activities in Tata Infinity Retail Company.
- 3. Best employee & star performer of the month of the month in Croma Infinity Retail Tata Enterprise (June and July 2014).

## **Declaration**

I hereby declare that the information furnished above is true to the best of my knowledge.

Place: Thane

Date: Sachin B. Shelke